RISM Collections at New York University Conferences Guide to the Records of New Perspectives on Caribbean Studies: Toward the 21st Century and Prospects for Caribbean Basin Integration (Conference held at Hunter College, CUNY, August 28-September 1, 1984) RISM.RG.16.(j)
New York University Archives
- Series VI. Conference Participants, November 1982 - November 1986, 141863
  - Roy Neehall correspondence, Feb - Aug 1984; 141914 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Rex Nettleford correspondence, Oct - Nov 1983; Feb - Aug 1984; 141913 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - David Nicholls correspondence, Oct 1983; Jan - Mar 1984; 141912 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Abioseh Davidson Nicol correspondence, clipping, Feb - May 1984; 141911 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Maurice A. Odle correspondence, abstract, Oct 1983; Jan - Jun 1984; undated; 141910 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Carl D. Parris correspondence, abstract, Jan - Aug 1984; undated; 141909 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Peter D. Phillips correspondence, abstract, Jan - Aug 1984; undated; 141908 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Ken Post correspondence, abstract, article, Jun - Dec 1983; Feb - Aug 1984; 141907 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Angel G. Quintero-Rivera correspondence, postcard, abstracts, Oct - Dec 1983; Jan - Aug 1984; Jan -85; 141906 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Roderick Rainford correspondence, Oct 1983; Jan - Sept 1984; 141905 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Kenneth Ramchand correspondence, Oct 1983; Jan - July 1984; 141904 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Rohlehr correspondence, Oct 1983; Jan - July 1984; 141903 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Margurite Ross-Barnett correspondence, greeting card, clippings, ephemera, Oct - Nov 1983; Jan - Aug 1984; 141902 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - James Rowe correspondence, Interciencia journal, Jan - Aug 1984; 141901 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Vera D. Rubin clippings, printed matter: The Nation, "Casa de las Americas," Patricia Higgins,Human Organization, Mar - Aug 1984; 141900 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Helen Safa correspondence, abstract, ephemera, Oct - Nov 1983; May - Aug 1984; undated; 141899 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Saskia Sassen-Koob correspondence, abstract, May - Aug 1984; undated; 141898 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Aaron Segal, Wallace C. Koehler correspondence, abstract, review essay, Jul 1984; Nov 1986; undated; 141897 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Andres Serbin correspondence, abstract, clippings, book reviews, ephemera, 1982; Sept - Dec 1983; Feb - Dec 1984; undated; 141896 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Shirley B. Seward, correspondence, May - Jun 1984; 141895 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Donna Shalala, correspondence, invitations, event brochures, ephemera, Jan - Apr 1984; undated; 141894 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Alan Simmons correspondence, May 1984; 141893 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Marilyn Silverman correspondence, abstract, Oct - Nov 1983; Feb - July 1984; 141892 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Harold Sims correspondence, Oct - Dec 1983; May - Jun 1984; 141891 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Rickey Singh correspondence, ephemera, Jan - July 1984; 141890 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Archie Singham brochures, correspondence, ephemera, Sept - Oct 1983; Jan - Jun 1984; 141889 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - M. G. Smith correspondence, greeting card, abstracts, articles and reprints, Oct - Dec 1982; Oct - Dec 1983; Jan - Sept 1984; undated; 141888 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - R. T. Smith correspondence, Oct - Dec 1983; Feb - Nov 1984; 141887 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jorge Sol correspondence, ephemera, Sep 1984; 141886 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Giorgio Solimano correspondence, curriculum vitae, Apr - July 1984; 141885 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - E. B. A. St. Cyr, John A. Spence, correspondence, mailgrams, ephemera, Apr - Aug 1984; 141884 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - John Stewart correspondence, ephemera, Oct - Dec 1983; May - Jun 1984; 141883 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Carl Stone correspondence, ephemera, Oct 1983; Jan - Jun 1984; 141882 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Constance Sutton correspondence, Oct - Nov 1983; Feb - May 1984; 141881 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Michael Thelwell correspondence, Oct 1983; 141880 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - C. Y. Thomas correspondence, print material, abstracts, curriculum vitae, ephemera, 1982; Oct 1983; Jan - Aug 1984; Dec -86; 141879 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope greeting card, correspondence, July - Sept 1984; 141878 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Tuden correspondence, July - Aug 1984; 141877 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Nelson Valdes correspondence, Oct 1983; Jan - Aug 1984; 141876 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Charles Wagley correspondence, Oct - Nov 1983; Jan - Sept 1984; 141875 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Derek Walcott correspondence, clippings, book review [C.L.R. James], print material, Oct - Nov 1983; Jan - Apr 1984; undated; 141874 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Alaka Walli correspondence, abstract, Oct 1983; Feb - Apr 1984; 141873 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - L.O. Watkins review essay, correspondence, Oct - Nov 1983; May - Aug 1984; 141872 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hilbourne A. Watson correspondence, abstracts, May - Aug 1984; 141871 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - John Wickham correspondence, article, Oct - Dec 1983; Feb - Sept 1984; 141870 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dessima Williams correspondence, greeting card, Jan - May 1984; undated; 141869 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence A. Wilson correspondence, abstract, mailgrams, pamphlet, May - Oct 1984; undated; 141868 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Winston Wiltshire correspondence, abstract, Oct 1983; Mar - July 1984; 141867 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Rosina Wiltshire-Brodber correspondence, abstract, draft material, Oct - Nov 1983; Feb - Aug 1984; 141866 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Eric R. Wolf correspondence, book reviews, Oct - Nov 1983; Jan - Aug 1984; undated; 141865 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Adolfo Aguilar correspondence, abstract, Oct 1984; undated; 141864 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Series VII. Clippings, January 1982 - October 1984, undated, 141826
  .5 linear feet (1 box), arranged chronologically. This series, which consists of clippings from U.S. and Caribbean papers, has been organized as three subseries. Subseries a. relates to grant funding, Subseries b. contains articles on a wide range of international topics, and Subseries c. consists of post-conference articles. Oversized clippings have been transferred to Series XV. Oversized materials.
  - Subseries a. Grant funding, 141853
    - "About Education -- What Must Be Done to Save the Humanities," The New York Times, Jan 1982; 141862 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "MacArthur Trust, A Philanthropic Maverick, Faces Divestiture and Discord," The New York Times, Aug 1983; 141861 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "U.S. Philanthropies Turn Concern to Arms Race," The New York Times, Mar 1984; 141860 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "90 Receive Sloan Foundation Grants," The New York Times, Mar 1984; 141859 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "Amending the National Science Foundation Act," Science, Vol. 224, Apr 1984; 141858 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "U.S. Aids Study of Vietnam Film," The New York Times, Jun 1984; 141857 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "Can It Be? Scientists Immune to the Fever?" The New York Times, Apr 1984; 141856 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Uncivil Liberties," The Nation, Aug 1984; Jun 1984; 141855 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "Teen Wins Prestigious Award," U.S.A. Today, undated; 141854 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Subseries b. International Topics, 141834
    - "Manley in the USA," Weekly Gleaner, May 1983; 141852 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Excerpts from the Caricom Perspective, Jan - Feb 1984; 141851 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "Scholars Will Focus on Latin American Jews," The New York Times, Mar 1984; 141850 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - "Student-Run Radio Show Is Focusing on America," The New York Times, Mar 1984; 141849 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Excerpts from the Caricom Perspective, Mar - Apr 1984; 141848 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "Turnout Cheers Democrats," The New York Times, Jun 1984; 141847 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Academic Team, Disputing Carter Study, Sees Affluent Future," The New York Times, Jun 1984; 141846 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "Latins Offer a Salvador Mediation Plan," The New York Times, Jul 1984; 141845 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Europeans and Latins To Discuss Closer Ties," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141844 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "The Myopia of Human Rights Advocates," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141843 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "U.S. Says Uganda Rights Abuses Are Among Most Grave in World," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141842 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "America's Athletic Imperialism," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141841 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "New Varieties of Hardy Rice Hold Promise," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141840 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "U.S. Paying $1.6 Million For Damaging Grenada," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141839 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Cheap Little Windmills Outdo High- Tech Giants," The New York Times, Aug 1984; 141838 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Maurice Bishop Speaks," Book Review, Carib News, Aug 1984; 141837 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - "For Mexicans, Concern Rises on Civil Rights," The New York Times, Sep 1984; 141836 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Protest Voiced at U.S. Exclusion Of Visitors Because of Their Ideas," The New York Times, Sep 1984; 141835 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Subseries c. Post-Conference, 141827
    - "Caribbean to come under close scrutiny," Barbados Advocate, May 1984; 141833 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - "On Future of Caribbean," The Nation, Jul 1984; 141832 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "A Unique Event," Rickey Singh, Our Caribbean","Three Honored," The Nation (Barbados), Sep 1984; 141831 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "Hunter College Honours W. Indians," The Sunday Gleaner, Sep 1984; 141830 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "NY Awards to Caribbean Artists", Oct 1984; 141829 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Investigative Levels re: Political Choices," Caribbean Contact, Oct 1984; 141828 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Series VIII. Photographs, August 28 - September 1, 1984 (at the Reed Foundation), 141528
  Approximately 1.0 linear feet (1 box, 1 binder). This series is comprised of 108 negatives, 3 contact sheets, 69 photographic prints, photocopies of 5 contact sheets, and one disc containing 180 image files in TIFF format. All images originate from black and white 35 mm film. The disc and the photographic prints are located in a separate binder labeled Notebook 14A. The contents of the disc are described in Subseries a., b., and c., and the photographic prints are described in Subseries d. Subseries a. contains digitized copies of the negatives in Folder 4; Subseries b. contains digitized copies of contact sheets in Folder 3; Subseries c. contains digitized copies of the photographic prints in Subseries d. Images in Subseries a., b., c., and d. have been arranged by conference session, and assigned consecutive ID numbers, e.g. "CC84-01." Digitized copies of photographic prints and corresponding original photographic prints have been assigned identical ID numbers.
  - Outline of panel sessions, conference presenters and titles of papers, Aug - Sept 1984; 141825 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Photocopies of contact sheets with notes on select images to be enlarged (five 8.5 x 11 sheets). Selected images correspond to prints in notebook 14A. [Original contact sheets are missing.], Aug - Sept 1984; 141824 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Contact sheets developed from negatives in Box 14, Folder 4 (three 8.5 x 11" sheets). [digitized copies on disc in notebook 14A, CC84-178 to CC84-180], Aug - Sept 1984; 141823 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Subseries a. Digitized Copies of Negatives, 170400
    - Session I. Plantation Society and The Contemporary Caribbean, 141812
      - l. to r.: Joseph Murphy, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141821 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-001)
      - l. to r.: Joseph Murphy, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Aug 29, 1984; 141820 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-002)
      - l. to r.: Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141819 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-003)
      - l. to r.: Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, C. Y. Thomas, Aug 29, 1984; 141818 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-004)
      - l. to r.: Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, C. Y. Thomas, Jay R. Mandle, Maurice A. Odle, Norman P. Girvan, Aug 29, 1984; 141817 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-005)
      - l. to r.: Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, C. Y. Thomas, Jay R. Mandle, Maurice A. Odle, Norman P. Girvan, Aug 29, 1984; 141816 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-006)
      - l. to r.: George L. Beckford, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Aug 29, 1984; 141815 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-007)
      - l. to r.: George L. Beckford, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141814 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-008)
      - l. to r.: Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, C. Y. Thomas, Jay R. Mandle, Maurice A. Odle, Norman P. Girvan, Aug 29, 1984; 141813 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-009)
      - George L. Beckford, Aug 29, 1984; 141792 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-010)
      - l. to r.: George L. Beckford, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141791 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-011)
      - l. to r.: George L. Beckford, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141790 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-012)
      - l. to r.: Val McComie, Vera D. Rubin, Aug 29, 1984; 141789 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-013)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Aug 29, 1984; 141788 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-014)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, Aug 29, 1984; 141787 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-015)
      - C. Y. Thomas, Aug 29, 1984; 141786 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-016)
      - l. to r.: Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Aug 29, 1984; 141785 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-017)
      - l. to r.: Vera D. Rubin, unidentified, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141784 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-018)
      - l. to r.: Patrick I. Gomes, Jay R. Mandle, Maurice A. Odle, Norman P. Girvan, Aug 29, 1984; 141783 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-019)
      - l. to r.: Val McComie, Lloyd Best, Patrick I. Gomes, Aug 29, 1984; 141782 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-020)
      - C.Y. Thomas, 170342 (Notebook 14A, File CC84-021)
      - l. to r.: Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individual, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141780 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-022)
      - l. to r.: Jean Casimir, George L. Beckford, Val McComie, Aug 29, 1984; 141779 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-023)
      - Vera D. Rubin, Aug 29, 1984; 141778 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-024)
      - l. to r.: Val McComie, Patrick I. Gomes, C. Y. Thomas, Aug 29, 1984; 141777 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-025)
      - l. to r.: Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jean Casimir, unidentified individual, Val McComie, unidentified individual, Aug 29, 1984; 141776 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-026)
      - l. to r.: unidentified individual, George L. Beckford, Aug 29, 1984; 141775 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-027)
      - l. to r.: C. Y. Thomas, unidentified, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jay R. Mandle, Norman P. Girvan, Aug 29, 1984; 141774 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-028)
      - l. to r.: C. Y. Thomas, Manuel Moreno Fraginals, Jay R. Mandle, Aug 29, 1984; 141773 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-029)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Lloyd Best, Aug 29, 1984; 141772 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-030)
    - Session II. Stratification, Pluralism and Sociopolitical Dynamics, 141771
      - l. to r.: Michel S. Laguerre, Angel G. Quintero-Rivera, Ken Post, Paget Henry, Aug 29, 1984; 141811 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-031)
      - foreground: Jean Casimir; background: l. to r.: M. G. Smith, Demetrio Boersner, Andres Serbin, Aug 29, 1984; 141810 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-032)
      - Jean Casimir, Aug 29, 1984; 141809 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-033)
      - l. to r.: M. G. Smith, Eric R. Wolf, Lloyd Braithwaite, Andres Serbin, Demetrio Boersner, Suzy Castor, Helen Safa, Aug 29, 1984; 141808 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-034)
    - Session III. Theoretical and Applied Issues in Social Organization, 141752
      - l. to r.: Neville Duncan, Frank McGlynn, Aug 29, 1984; 141770 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-035)
      - l. to r.: Neville Duncan, Frank McGlynn, Diane J. Austin, Locksley Edmondson, Aug 29, 1984; 141769 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-036)
      - l. to r.: Eddie Greene, Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Constance Sutton, Robert A. Manners, Carl D. Parris, Aug 29, 1984; 141768 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-037)
      - l. to r.: Frank McGlynn, Diane J. Austin, Locksley Edmondson, Aug 29, 1984; 141767 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-038)
      - foreground: Neville Duncan; background: l. to r.: Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Constance Sutton, Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141766 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-039)
      - foreground: Diane J. Austin; background: Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141765 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-040)
      - foreground: Diane J. Austin; background: Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141764 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-041)
      - foreground: Diane J. Austin; background: Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141763 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-042)
      - Constance Sutton, Aug 29, 1984; 141762 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-043)
      - Constance Sutton, Aug 29, 1984; 141761 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-044)
      - l. to r.: Eddie Greene, Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Constance Sutton, Robert A. Manners, Carl D. Parris, Judy Butler, Frank McGlynn, Aug 29, 1984; 141760 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-045)
      - foreground: Carl D. Parris; background: Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141759 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-046)
      - foreground: Carl D. Parris; background: Robert A. Manners, Aug 29, 1984; 141758 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-047)
      - foreground: Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope; background: Carl D. Parris, Aug 29, 1984; 141757 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-048)
      - foreground: Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope; background: Carl D. Parris, Aug 29, 1984; 141756 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-049)
      - foreground: Eddie Greene; background: Carl D. Parris, Aug 29, 1984; 141755 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-050)
      - Eddie Greene, Aug 29, 1984; 141754 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-051)
      - l. to r.: Frank McGlynn, Diane J. Austin, Locksley Edmondson, Neville Duncan, Aug 29, 1984; 141753 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-052)
    - Session IV. Processes of Ethnicity, 141731
      - Edmundo Gordon, Aug 30, 1984; 141751 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-053)
      - l. to r.: Elizabeth Halpern, Judy Butler, Lucille Mair, Aug 30, 1984; 141750 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-054)
      - Edmundo Gordon, Aug 30, 1984; 141749 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-055)
      - l. to r.: Adolfo Aguilar, Philippe Bourgois, Aug 30, 1984; 141748 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-056)
      - l. to r.: Lambros Comitas, Arthur Tuden, Aug 30, 1984; 141747 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-057)
      - June Nash, Aug 30, 1984; 141746 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-058)
      - l. to r.: Judy Butler, Lucille Mair, Aug 30, 1984; 141745 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-059)
      - Unidentified individual, Aug 30, 1984; 170396 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-060)
      - Elizabeth Halpern, Aug 30, 1984; 170397 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-061)
      - Elizabeth Halpern, Aug 30, 1984; 170398 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-062)
      - Adolfo Aguilar, Aug 30, 1984; 141741 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-063)
      - Adolfo Aguilar, Aug 30, 1984; 141740 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-064)
      - Adolfo Aguilar, Aug 30, 1984; 141739 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-065)
      - Arthur Tuden, Aug 30, 1984; 141738 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-066)
      - Arthur Tuden, Aug 30, 1984; 141737 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-067)
      - l. to r.: unidentified individual, Archie Singham, undated; 141736 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-068)
      - Marilyn Silverman, Aug 30, 1984; 141735 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-069)
      - Marilyn Silverman, Aug 30, 1984; 141734 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-070)
      - Marilyn Silverman, Aug 30, 1984; 141733 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-071)
      - Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Aug 30, 1984; 141732 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-072)
    - Session V. Nationalism, Independence and Creative Florescence, 141715
      - l. to r.: George Lamming, unidentified individual, Wilfred Cartey, Aug 30, 1984; 141730 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-073)
      - l. to r.: Gordon Rohlehr, Frank E. Manning, Aug 30, 1984; 141729 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-074)
      - Unidentified individual, Aug 30, 1984; 141728 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-075)
      - Merle Hodge, Aug 30, 1984; 141727 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-076)
      - Merle Hodge, Aug 30, 1984; 141726 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-077)
      - Neville Linton, Aug 30, 1984; 141725 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-078)
      - Wilfred Cartey, Aug 30, 1984; 141724 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-079)
      - Wilfred Cartey, Aug 30, 1984; 141723 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-080)
      - Wilfred Cartey, Aug 30, 1984; 141722 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-081)
      - l. to r.: Rex Nettleford, Errol Hill, Aug 30, 1984; 141721 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-082)
      - l. to r.: Rex Nettleford, Errol Hill, Merle Hodge, Aug 30, 1984; 141720 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-083)
      - Rex Nettleford, Aug 30, 1984; 141719 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-084)
      - Frank E. Manning, Aug 30, 1984; 141718 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-085)
      - Unidentified individual, Aug 30, 1984; 141717 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-086)
      - Gordon Rohlehr, Aug 30, 1984; 141716 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-087)
    - Unknown Location and Date, 170401
      - l. to r.: Rosina Wiltshire-Brodber, Ursula Braithwaite, undated; 170403 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-088)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170404 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-089)
      - l. to r.: Gordon Rohlehr, Don Mills, undated; 170405 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-090)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170406 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-091)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170407 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-092)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170408 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-093)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170409 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-094)
      - Unidentified individual, undated; 170410 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-095)
      - l. to r.: Vera D. Rubin, Mighty Sparrow, Archie Singham, undated; 170411 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-096)
      - Mighty Sparrow, undated; 170412 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-097)
      - l. to r.: Mighty Sparrow, Archie Singham, undated; 170413 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-098)
      - l. to r.: Mighty Sparrow, Archie Singham, undated; 170414 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-099)
      - Mighty Sparrow, undated; 170415 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-100)
      - l. to r.: Archie Singham, Mighty Sparrow, Lucille Mair, undated; 170416 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-101)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 1], undated; 170419 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-102)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 2], undated; 170420 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-103)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 3], undated; 170421 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-104)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 4], undated; 170422 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-105)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 5], undated; 170423 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-106)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 6], undated; 170424 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-107)
      - Unidentified individuals [Roll 43 # 7], undated; 170425 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-108)